<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30DaysOfSuccess</string>
    <string name="day">Day %d</string>
    <string name="day_1_quote">Do not let your difficulties fill you with anxiety, after all it is only in the darkest nights that stars shine more brightly.</string>
    <string name="day_2_quote">Nothing hurts a good soul and a kind heart more than to live amongst people who cannot understand it.</string>
    <string name="day_3_quote">When the world pushes you to your knees, you\'re in the perfect position to pray</string>
    <string name="day_4_quote">The best deed of a great man is to forgive and forget.</string>
    <string name="day_5_quote">A graceful refusal is better than a lengthy promise</string>
    <string name="day_6_quote">He who trusts the world, the world betrays him.</string>
    <string name="day_7_quote">The disease of the heart is worse than the disease of the body.</string>
    <string name="day_8_quote">Backbiting is the attempt of one who is incapable of doing better himself.</string>
    <string name="day_9_quote">A wise man always has something to say, whereas a fool always needs to say something.</string>
    <string name="day_10_quote">Surely silence can sometimes be the most eloquent reply.</string>
    <string name="day_11_quote">Take Care Of Your Tongue Like The Way You Take Care Of Gold &amp; Silver.</string>
    <string name="day_12_quote">Beware of speaking too much, for it increases mistakes and engenders boredom.</string>
    <string name="day_13_quote">It’s never the value of water but thirst, it’s never the value of life but death and it’s never about the friendship but trust.</string>
    <string name="day_14_quote">The nourishment of body is food, while the nourishment of the soul is feeding others.</string>
    <string name="day_15_quote">There is no rest for the person who has envy, and there is no love for the person who has bad manners.</string>
    <string name="day_16_quote">You must be humble, as it is one of the greatest [forms of] worship.</string>
    <string name="day_17_quote">Not to have a thing is less humiliating than to beg it.</string>
    <string name="day_18_quote">To fight against one’s desires is the greatest of all fights.</string>
    <string name="day_19_quote">When you get ill do not get nervous about it and try as much as possible to be hopeful.</string>
    <string name="day_20_quote">The strongest amongst you is he who subdues his self.</string>
    <string name="day_21_quote">Wealth and greed are the roots of all evils.</string>
    <string name="day_22_quote">Tears only dry up as a result of hardness of the heart, and the hearts only harden as a result of frequent sinning</string>
    <string name="day_23_quote">Riches without faith are the greatest poverty.</string>
    <string name="day_24_quote">The group with it\'s impurities is better than sectarianism with it\'s purity</string>
    <string name="day_25_quote">who accompany ignorants, lives in misery.</string>
    <string name="day_26_quote">Someone who can not find a good friend is weak. and someone who looses a good friend is even weaker.</string>
    <string name="day_27_quote">There is no wealth like knowledge, no poverty like ignorance.</string>
    <string name="day_28_quote">Body is purified by water. Ego by tears. Intellect is purified by knowledge. And soul is purified with love.</string>
    <string name="day_29_quote">Do not follow the majority, follow the truth.</string>
    <string name="day_30_quote">A little Knowledge removes a lot of arrogance!</string>
</resources>